# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rake db:seed (or created alongside the db with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   cities = City.create([{ name: 'Chicago' }, { name: 'Copenhagen' }])
#   Mayor.create(name: 'Emanuel', city: cities.first)


# Create FAQs
Faq.create(question:"How do I make a claim with Aviva?", answer: "It is important you contact the Customer Service Helpline before you undertake any specialist consultations or receive any private medical treatment. On referral from your GP please call the helpline on 0800 092 8264 or 02381 247 352 so they can confirm: -The details of your membership -The treatment you require is covered under the terms of your policy -Your recommended specialist and hospital is recognised by us; or -If there are any limits that apply to your cover which you should be aware of. Aviva will issue you with a claims reference number please ensure you take this to any appointments you have. There may be occasions where we ask for further medical information in order to make a decision on your claim; however we will keep you informed of this throughout the claim process. ")
Faq.create(question:"Do I need to be refered by a gp?", answer: "In the UK the majority of specialists will ask for a referral from your GP prior to agreeing to see you. -If you are currently registered with a GP then you should go and see them if you feel unwell - If you are not registered with a GP, you are entitled to see a private GP. Please contact Aviva and they will help you with this -If it is an emergency or out of business hours we recommend that you go to your nearest NHS facility as they are best placed to help in these circumstances - If you know the name of the specialist you would like to see then please contact Aviva and we will advise you how to progress your claim. If you need to register with a GP please look at the NHS website which provides information regarding how to do this. Please also refer to useful information page for the list of private facilities with emergency cover and those that have GP services attached to them.")
Faq.create(question:"Can I still use the NHS if I want to?", answer:"Yes, if you are currently entitled to use the NHS and would like to continue to use these services please do so. The benefits you are entitled to through Aviva will still be available if you decide to transfer to private care at any time during your treatment. You are entitled to £100 cash incentive for every night you stay on the NHS and receive free treatment up to a maximum of 30 nights.")

Faq.create(question:"Where can I find out what hospitals I can use?", answer:"Additionally you can alo use any NHS hospital with private facilities in the UK. If you have any questions about which hospital to use or which specialist to see please call Aviva. The hospital list of all private hospitals and clinics, including dental clinics that applies to your policy is detailed in your member literature. You can view a copy of your hospital list online at www.uksacb.org or alternatively you can request further details from the helpline. Additionally you can also use any NHS hospital with private facilities in the UK. If you have any questions about which hospital to use or which specialist to see please call Aviva.")
Faq.create(question:"Am I covered for pregnancy and childbirth?", answer:"Yes, you are covered for pregnancy and childbirth including the appointments and scans required as part of your care. If you have any questions regarding pregnancy and childbirth please refer to the useful information page or alternatively call Aviva.")
Faq.create(question:"Am I covered for dental treatment?", answer:"Yes, dental treatment is covered under the scheme up to £5,000 per person per policy year. This includes cover for check-ups and examinations, fillings and tooth extractions. There is additional benefit for treatment for temporomandibular joint disorder up to £5,000. We recommend that you contact Aviva before starting any dental treatment to check that it is covered.")

Faq.create(question:"Am I covered for optical treatment?", answer:"Yes, there is cover for optical treatment up to £400 per person per policy year. This includes cover for routine check-ups, examinations and glasses or contact lenses up to the above limit. You will need to pay for this treatment and send in the receipt with your name and Saudi ID number clearly written on it to enable prompt payment.")
Faq.create(question:"Will you pay for interpreters?", answer:"Aviva do not cover the cost of interpreters required for any appointments you may have.")
Faq.create(question:"Am I covered in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia?", answer:"Yes, you are entitled to the same cover as you are in the UK. The cover in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia is provided by Malath Cooperative Insurance and Reinsurance Company. Please note that all benefit limits apply in combination between the UK and the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.")

Faq.create(question:"How do I know if I am covered?", answer:"If you have registered with the Royal Kingdom of Saudi Arabia Cultural Bureau in the UK, you are automatically covered by the Aviva Private Medical Insurance scheme. If you are unsure of your cover please call Aviva.")
Faq.create(question:"What should I do if I need to change my personal details?", answer:"If you need to change any of your personal details, e.g. your address, please call Aviva and we will update your records. It is important that you have a valid UK address, please refer to the useful information page for guidance on this.")
Faq.create(question:"What do I do if I receive any invoices for medical treatment authorised by Aviva?", answer:"Aviva operates direct billing with most doctors and hospitals and they will send their invoices direct to Aviva UK Health. However, if you do receive any bills for treatment that has been authorised by Aviva please send them to: Aviva UK Health P.O. Box 443, Eastleigh, SO53 3WZ. Please ensure that you write your name, Saudi ID and policy number, which is 961BBS, on all invoices you send in to Aviva.")

Faq.create(question:"What should I do if I need to claim a refund from Aviva?", answer:"In order to ensure prompt payment please send the original receipt with your name, Saudi ID and policy number, which is 961BBS, clearly written on all receipts. Please make a copy of the receipt and keep this for your records. The refund is made by cheque and will be posted to your home address.")
Faq.create(question:"Who can I call if I have any queries?", answer:"If you have any queries please call Aviva on 0800 092 8264 or 02381 247 352. Alternatively you can refer to the useful information page on this website as well as refer to your member guide for full details of the policy and benefits available to you.")
Faq.create(question:"What do I do if I haven’t received my policy documents?", answer: "Please note that you can download a copy of your Aviva member guide from www.uksacb.org. In order to access treatment using your Aviva policy we recommend that you call Aviva and we will issue you with a claims reference number, this is all you will need for treatment in the UK.")

Faq.create(question:"What do I need to do if I change my address?", answer:"If you move house, you will need to call Aviva to advise your new address. Unless we have your correct address, you will not receive reimbursement cheques or any correspondence. Please use the following link for assistance and accuracy: http://www.royalmail.com/postcode-finder")
Faq.create(question: "What happens when my sponsorship ends?", answer:"If your sponsorship ends because you are no longer studying, you will no longer be covered by the Medical insurance.")
Faq.create(question: "Do you pay for accommodation for family members whilst I am in hospital?", answer:"Aviva will cover the cost for 1 family member to stay with you, if necessary, if you are admitted into hospital.")

